and that is 365 ready help the toy is on
digital health and life insurance plan
yearly renewable plan
major coverage number one is some
critical illness that covers top 6
critical illnesses that includes cancer
heart attack coronary artery bypass
surgery
stroke kidney failure and number six end
stage lung disease take note the Topo
eye subjects are term and conditions
I 150
000.
diagnosis
insured 150
000.
I am life insurance worth 150
000. 150
000 and I think beneficiary take note
whichever comes first
critical illness at life insurance
We Begin benefit and then Mata terminate
on policy
depending from 18 to 35 and premium I
1499 Murano computer for as low as four
pesos a day
critical illness
illness worth 150 000 life insurance
coverage no work 150
000.
[Music]
36 to 45
and premium I
2999 8 pesos per day
36 to 45. important to know number one
pre-existing condition is not covered or
not payable but a critical illness
diagnosis
number two 90 days waiting period
because
first 90 days
the critical illness
covered unless
90 days
and top six critical illnesses number
three Independence
multiple products in 365 ready health is
up to age 45. next disadvantage are you
whichever comes first
diagnosis
critical illness or the life insurance
coverage advantage
affordable shot for as low as
1499 18 to 35 at 36 to 45 Naman
299. my access is a critical illness
coverage
[Music]
by a credit card or debit card adding
Mastercard or a Visa card medical
assessment or your medical examination
policy contract via e contract or
electronically contract renewable
long term not commitment here's my
advice before getting this product
number one is
number
three
specific coverage NATO
money life financial advisor at home
please don't hesitate to message or
contact the manager them and Mom K
lubrin Manulife cabanatuan thank you so
much for watching hope to see you soon
foreign